晚上好
Good evening.
我是你们的客座讲师  谢尔顿·库珀博士
I'm your guest lecturer, Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
我还等着掌声呢
I was expecting applause,
不过"王八之气"震慑后的安静也挺好的
but I suppose stunned silence is equally appropriate.
我之所以今晚愿意来给你们上课
I agreed to speak to you this evening,
是因为有人告诉我你们是这所学校里的
because I was told that you're the best and the brightest
博士生中最优秀最聪明的
of this university's doctoral candidates.
当然  这就像是说
Hmm. Of course, that's like saying
你们是氢原子中最重要的电子一样
you are the most important electron in a hydrogen atom.
因为  你们想啊
'Cause, you see,
氢原子只有一个电子
there's only one electron in a hydrogen atom.
这也算最优秀最聪明啊  我的老天爷
Best and brightest, my sweet patootie.
好吧  开始上课
All right, let's begin.
请举手告诉我  在座的哪位
Show of hands, who here is familiar
对拓扑绝缘体的概念比较熟悉
with the concept of topological insulators?
别自欺欺人了
Don't kid yourselves.
我又看到了一条谢尔顿课上的学生的微博
I found another tweet from a student at Sheldon's lecture.
"库珀博士选择的话题相当无聊
"Dr. Cooper has taken a relatively boring subject
并且他成功地升级到了令人无法忍受的地步
and managed to make it completely insufferable.
另外  他看起来像只大昆虫"
Plus, he looks like a giant insect."
听着  听听这条
Look. Listen to this one.
"爱因斯坦的理论是不是揭示了为什么
"Does Einstein's theory explain why time flies
当你快乐时时间飞逝
when you're having fun,
而当你听库珀博士说话时
but when you're listening to Dr. Cooper,
时间就慢得要命"
it falls out of the sky, dead?"
有人拍了照
Ooh, somebody took pictures
还上传到了Flickr上
and uploaded them to their Flickr account.
哇
Wow.
你要怎么做才能让整个演讲大厅里的人
How do you get an entire lecture hall
同时冲你竖中指啊
to flip you off at the same time?
显然啊  如果你是谢尔顿的话
Apparently, if you're Sheldon,
你需要做的只是转个身而已
all you need to do is turn your back.
莱纳德  你家Wi-Fi坏了吗
Hey, Leonard, is your Wi-Fi down?
我连不上啊
I can't get on.
哦  谢尔顿把密码改了
Oh, Sheldon changed the password.
现在是"佩妮是个蹭网的"
It's now "Penny is a freeloader."
别加空格
No spaces.
多谢  你们在干嘛呢
Thanks. What are you guys doing?
谢尔顿今晚在学校里上课
Sheldon gave a lecture at the university tonight.
我们在看评论
We're reading the reviews.
他表现如何啊
Oh. How'd he do?
想象一下"兴登堡"号飞艇爆炸加上切尔诺贝利核泄漏
Well, picture the Hindenburg meets Chernobyl
加上三里岛核泄漏再加上《电子世界争霸战2》
meets Three Mile Island meets Tron 2.
有那么糟啊
That bad, huh?
念一下这个女生的微博
Read this woman's tweet.
"听库珀博士讲课
"Listening to Dr. Cooper
让我又想自残了"
has made me want to start cutting myself again""
是吧
Yeah.
晚上好  莱纳德  霍华德  拉杰
Good evening, Leonard, Howard, Raj,
蹭网的
freeloader.
课上得怎么样啊
So, how'd the lecture go?
一言以蔽之  大获全胜啊
In a word, triumphant.
真的吗  大获全胜
Really? Triumphant?
可不是吗  你们真该亲眼看看那群孩子
Oh, yes, you should have seen those young people.
求知若渴  贪婪地聆听我的教诲
Thirsty for knowledge, drinking in my wisdom.
我今天也许改变了不少人的人生
I may have changed a few lives today.
求你让我告诉他吧
Oh, please let me tell him.
我不知道行不行啊  我答应了霍华德的
I don't know, I kind of promised Howard.
告诉我啥
Tell me what?
其实呢  我们应该一起分享这一刻
Actually, we should all share the moment.
拉杰  你来吧
Raj, if you would.
关于我的课的微薄啊
Oh, tweets about my lecture.
这条很不公平
That's rather unfair.
这条太伤人了
That's downright cruel.
而且  昆虫都有六条腿
Plus, insects have six legs.
我不是很清楚"KMN"这个缩写是啥意思
Yeah, I'm not familiar with the acronym "KMN""
根据语境  我们觉得是"快杀了我吧"
From the context, we think it means "kill me now."
我觉得每个人都有权表达自己的观点
Well, I suppose everyone's entitled to their own opinion.
我还是去睡觉吧
I think I'll turn in.
反正我也不想教那群榆木脑袋了
I didn't want to teach those poopy heads, anyway.
顺便说一句  我觉得这句话是达斯·维达
FYI, I think that's what Darth Vader said
在建造死星之前说的
just before he started building the Death Star.
生活大爆炸
第四季第十四集
谢尔顿还在郁闷吗
Sheldon still moping?
是啊  好奇怪  就算他一开始就不想
Yeah, it's weird. Even though he didn't want
给这帮学生上课
to give the lecture in the first place,
被他们拒绝还是打击挺大的
being rejected by those students really hit him hard.
这感觉我深有体会
I know the feeling.
就好像无意中走进了一家同性恋酒吧
It's like accidentally walking into a gay bar
然后发现没人对你有兴趣
and then having no one hit on you.
这  这是我一个朋友的经历
It-It happened to a friend of mine.
你们还好吗
Are you guys doing okay?
莱纳德和我还好
Leonard and I are fine,
但我觉得拉杰现在真的急需一位小妞
but I think Raj needs to meet a girl really soon.
这不是什么难事
Well, that shouldn't be too hard.
他这么可爱
He's such a cutie.
谢谢夸奖  但是"可爱"是形容小兔子的
Thank you, but "cute" is for bunnies.
我想要能吸引异性
I want to be something with sex appeal,
就像  就像拉布拉多犬一样
like... like a labradoodle.
拉布拉多犬
Labradoodle?
我们估计得从头考虑你的问题了
We might be starting to zero in on your problem.
别听他们的
Don't you listen to them.
你对异性有足够的吸引力
You've got plenty of sex appeal.
你真这么觉得吗
You really think so?
是啊  你好性感哦
Yeah. You're a hottie.
谢谢  伯纳黛特
Well, thanks, Bernadette.
顺便告诉你们
And just for the record,
拉布拉多犬是防过敏的
labradoodles are hypo-allergenic,
这对于那些深受动物毛屑困扰的人来说很性感
which is a very sexy quality to those troubled by animal dander.
你觉得怎么样
So, what do you think?
很炫的视觉效果  但是我还是不高兴
It's a charming illusion, but it does not cheer me up.
就算我这么做都没用吗
Not even when I do this?
没用
No.
这是我搞怪的压箱底招了
Well, that was the last arrow in my quiver of whimsy.
你知不知道  教书是我自从1989年3月
Do you realize that teaching is the first thing
做引体向上失败以后
I've failed at since my ill-fated attempt
搞砸的第一件事
to complete a chin-up in March of 1989?
如果这次丢人的经历
If this humiliating experience
真的让你很困扰的话
is really troubling you,
我们还是有办法解决的
there are things we could do about it.
比如
For instance?
首先想到的
Well, the first thing that comes to mind
就是隔离你大脑里
is isolating the part of your brain
负责存储记忆的部分  然后用激光切掉它
where the memory is stored and destroying it with a laser.
嗯  不行
Hmm, no.
你一不留神
One slip of the hand,
我就只能坐在工程学院里
and suddenly I'm sitting in the Engineering Department,
和沃罗威茨一起捣鼓些小玩意儿了
building doodads with Wolowitz.
好吧
All right.
你有没有考虑过提高你的社交技能呢
Have you considered improving your socialization skills,
好让你
thus allowing you
更有效地和别人交流
to communicate more effectively with other people?
这难道不是他们的负担吗
Isn't that their burden?
我一直都是瞩目的焦点
I'm the one with something interesting to say.
没错  但是从本质上来讲
Fair enough, but in its essence,
教书是一门表演艺术
teaching is a performance art.
在教室这一范例中
In the classroom paradigm,
教师有交流的责任
the teacher has the responsibility to communicate,
也有娱乐和吸引学生的责任
as well as entertain and engage.
我感觉你在循循善诱啊
I sense that you're trying to slow-walk me to an epiphany.
你为何不直奔主题呢
Would you mind very much jumping to it?
也许你该考虑一下学学表演
Perhaps you should consider taking acting lessons.
学表演
Acting lessons.
有意思
Interesting.
如果我能表现得好像我关心我的学生们
It might help if I could act as though I care
在意他们学没学会  没准儿还有点儿用
about my students and whether or not they learn.
佩妮
Penny.
佩妮  佩妮
Penny. Penny.
干嘛
What?
你是个"演员"  对吧
You're an "actress," correct?
我不是"演员"
I'm not an "actress."
我就是演员
I'm an actress.
好吧
All right.
你是个演员
You're an actress.
我需要你教教我
I need you to teach me.
你想上一节表演课
You want an acting lesson?
没准儿得两节  我想学精一点儿
Perhaps two. I'd like to master the craft.
你怎么忽然想到这个的
Okay, where is this coming from?
有人建议我说  表演技巧
It has been suggested to me that acting techniques
能够提高我的教学水平
could improve my lecturing, at which,
如果有人相信那些微博和博客的话
if certain tweets and blogs are to be believed,
我貌似"不很擅长教学"
I "suck the big one."
啊  我都看过了  写得很好玩
Yeah, I saw those. They were funny.
我还打印了一些出来  贴在冰箱上了
I printed a few out and put 'em on my fridge.
那咱们什么时候开始上课
So, when could we start?
好吧  先把话说清楚了
Okay, just to be clear.
你找我帮忙是因为我会一些
You are asking me for help because I know something
你这位聪慧的谢尔顿·库珀博士不会的东西
that the brilliant Dr. Sheldon Cooper doesn't.
你这样解释也行
I suppose that's one way to look at it.
我认为这是唯一的解释了
I think it's the only way to look at it.
你到底帮不帮我嘛
Are you going to help me or not?
考虑看看  我只是比较享受这段前戏
Probably. I'm just enjoying the foreplay.
这是不是就意味着你不会再嘲笑我的演艺事业了
Does this mean you are done mocking my acting career?
真不好意思  我以为你由演员
Oh, I'm sorry, I thought making the transition
转变为表演课老师
from actor to acting teacher
就已经意味着
was the signal that one's career
你的事业走到了尽头了
had reached the end of the road.
算了吧
Forget it.
我付你四十美金
I'll pay you $40.
周六早上九点  带现金来
Saturday, 9:00 a.m. Bring cash.
拉杰  我有好消息要宣布
Raj, I have amazing news!
什么好消息
What?
以色列的魏茨曼研究所刚刚通知我
I just got offered a fellowship
他们给我提供了学术奖学金邀我过去
at the Weitzmann Institute in Israel.
-伙计  这太棒了  -就是
- Dude, that's incredible!  - I know.
唯一的问题是  我得离开两年
The only thing is, I'm gonna be gone for two years.
我会想你的
Aw, I'm gonna miss you.
你跟他一起去吗
Are you going with him?
我得留在这上学
I have to stay here for school.
我们就是来找你谈这件事的
That's what we're here to talk to you about.
你知道  伯纳黛特也是有需求的
You see, Bernadette has needs.
什么需求
What kind of needs?
性需求
Sexual needs.
大部分都还比较正常
Most of them regular,
但也有些比较狂野的
some of them kind of messed up.
所以  我不在的时候
So, while I'm gone,
就得靠你来满足她了
you're going to have to satisfy her.
你同意吗
What do you say?
乐意之至
I say okey-dokey.
你这么认真地想什么呢
What ya thinking so hard about?
我只是在想我绝对不是同性恋
Just that I'm definitely not gay.
佩妮
Penny!
佩妮  佩妮
Penny! Penny!
出什么事了
What's wrong?
没事  我在演戏而已
Nothing. I was acting.
你在演戏
You were acting.
没错  我为了今天要上的课做了很多预习
Yes. In preparation for today's studies,
我读了斯坦尼斯拉夫斯基的《演员的准备》
I read Stanislavski's An Actor Prepares,
斯特拉·阿德勒的《演戏的技术》
Stella Adler's The Technique of Acting,
犹他·哈根的《尊重表演艺术》
Uta Hagen's Respect for Acting,
和亨利·温克勒的《欸, 我是演员》
and Henry Winkler's Ayyy, I'm an Actor.
真不错
Well, good for you.
进来吧
Come on in.
我们怎么开始
How shall we begin?
我认为我们可以
Well, I thought we'd start
先做一些基础的动作练习
with some basic movement exercises.
就是稍微热热身
You know, get our bodies warmed up a little.
好吧
All right.
我想让你放松
So I just want you to relax
随意的扭动一下身体
and kind of move around in the space.
你觉得怎么自然就怎么来
You know, just do whatever feels natural.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
你说让我觉得怎么自然就怎么来
You said to do whatever feels natural.
我这样就挺自然的
This feels natural.
肯定比你在做的那些动作
Certainly more natural
要自然得多
than what you're doing.
拜托  你得配合我
Come on, you got to work with me.
我们要跟我们的身体建立联系
We need to get connected with our bodies.
佩妮  我和我的身体
Penny, my body and I have a relationship
在双方都很酷并且保持一定距离的情况下
that works best when we maintain a cool,
才能运作的最好
wary distance from each other.
好吧  就当咱们已经热过身了吧
All right, let's just say we've warmed up.
你是"老师"  你说了算
You're the "teacher" .
好吧  你要是想跟你的学生
Okay. One of the things that might help you
建立沟通  其中一个有效的办法
in connecting with your students
就是要自然一些
is being a little more spontaneous.
所以咱们试试即兴表演怎么样
So why don't we try some improvisation?
当然好啦  反正
Why not? It seems like
你整个教学过程也都是在即兴表演
you're improvising your entire curriculum.
这主要练习的就是倾听和反应能力
This is all about listening and responding.
明白
Gotcha.
我要创造一个角色
I'm going to create a character
和一个场景  你准备好了就加入我的表演
and a situation, and you just jump in when you feel it.
-好的  -那开始了
- All right.  - All right.
开拍
Action.
好吧  这不是在演电影
Okay, it's not a movie.
这只是即兴表演  所以用不着叫"开拍"
It's improv. So no one calls "action" .
你还真教了我点东西呢
Hey, you taught me something.
谁能想到会有这么一天
Who would have thought it?
好吧
Okay.
不  货还没送到呢
Uh, no, the shipment has not arrived,
我真的很急着要那批鞋子
and I really need those shoes.
那可是我卖的最好的货
They are my biggest seller.
没错  六到十码的女鞋
Yes, ladies sizes six through ten.
谢谢  抱歉
Thank you. Oh, sorry.
我得挂了  有客人上门了  再见
I have to go. I have a customer. Bye-bye.
有什么可以帮到你的吗
Hi. Can I help you?
请给我来一杯冻酸奶  谢谢
I'd like a frozen yogurt, please.
酸奶
Yogurt?
好吧  没问题
Okay, sure.
还好我们又卖鞋又卖酸奶
Luckily, we sell both shoes and yogurt here.
是吗
You do?
是啊  你抬头看看我们的招牌
Yes. Look up at the sign,
你还要记着  即兴表演就是要说是
and remember, improv is always about saying yes.
好吧
All right.
是耶
Yes.
我看到招牌了
I see a sign.
上面写着"卡马里奥州精神病院"
It says "Camarillo State Mental Hospital" .
什么
What?
只有这个理由才能解释
It's the only explanation I can come up with
你怎么会认为自己又卖鞋又卖酸奶
for why you think you sell shoes and yogurt.
好吧  这样好了
Okay, you know what?
咱们换个即兴表演的主题
Let's just try a different improv. Uh..
这次咱俩演两个
Oh, this time we will be two winos
住在高速公路天桥下的酒鬼好了
living under a freeway overpass.
我们都可以用道具了
Oh, and we're going to use props?
必须的
You bet.
我也是有梦想的  知道吗
I had dreams, you know.
我想出名
I was gonna be famous.
让我家乡的人都看看  我也能出人头地
Show everybody back home I could be someone.
可你看看我现在这样
Now look at me.
喝点吗
Want some?
你有冻酸奶吗
You have any frozen yogurt?
我还是不明白
I'm still not adjusted
幻想频道怎么会是这样拼写
to how the SyFy channel spells their name now.
S-y-F-y  那就成"饭想"了
S-y-F-y. That's "siffy" .
喂
Hello?
天啊  他没事吧
Oh, my God! Is he okay?
-出什么事了  -等一下  等一下
- What happened?  - Hang on. Hang on.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thank you.
霍华德骑摩托车的时候被一辆卡车给撞了
Howard was on his scooter, and got hit by a truck.
他现在情况危殆
He's in critical condition.
不
Oh, no!
你们听说了吗
Did you hear?
太可怕了
Isn't it terrible?
你见到他了吗
Have you seen him?
他们不让我进去
They wouldn't let me in.
我的霍霍呀
Oh, my Howie.
不会有事的  不会有事的
It'll be okay. It'll be okay.
不会有事的
It'll be okay.
是霍华德
It's Howard.
喂  霍华德
Howard, hello.
拉杰  是你吗
Raj, is that you?
是的  我就在这  兄弟  你还好吗
Yeah, I'm right here, buddy. How are you?
听我说
Shh, shh. Listen to me.
我撑不过了
I'm not gonna make it.
不  不  不  别这么说
No, no, no, don't say that.
你会没事的
You're going to be all right.
拉杰  我时间不多了  好好听我说
Raj, I don't have time. Now, pay attention.
我最后的愿望就是你要好好照顾伯纳黛特
My last wish is that you look after Bernadette.
当然了  当然了
Of course, of course.
不过你说"照顾"是指
Now when you say "look after", you mean...
性方面的
Sexually.
对不起  伯纳黛特  我得听他亲口说出来
Excuse me, Bernadette. I have to hear it from him.
性需求
Sexually.
哦了  保重啦
Got it. Take care.
我别无选择
I guess I have no choice
只能在余生  一而再再而三
but to make sweet, guilt-free love to you
毫无罪恶地跟你享受甜蜜爱欲
over and over again for the rest of my life.
这也是我亲耳所闻的
That's how I heard it.
又或者可以取名为"幻仙"
Or it could be "sy-fee."
你说什么
What?
S-y-F-y. "幻仙"
S-y-F-y. "Sy-fee."
好吧
Oh, right.
给力
Good one.
对了  你有时间看一遍我给你的那部电影吗
So, did you get a chance to go over the scene I gave you?
看了  但是我不喜欢
Yes. I didn't care for it.
《朱门巧妇》可是美国经典中的经典
Okay, Cat on a Hot Tin Roof is an American classic.
传奇汉堡也是
So is the McRib sandwich.
可我照样也不喜欢它
I don't care for that, either.
好吧  那在场景学习方面  你到底想怎么做
Fine. What would you rather do as a scene study?
很高兴你能这么问
I'm glad you asked.
我擅自把我
I took the liberty
十岁那年写的《星际迷航》同人小说
of adapting a Star Trek fan fiction novella
改编成一部独幕剧
I wrote when I was ten into a one-act play.
而你觉得比田纳西·威廉姆斯写的强多了
And you think it's better than Tennessee Williams?
为什么不留给后代去决定呢
Why don't we leave that for future generations to decide?
《那些谢尔顿未曾到过的地方》
Where No Sheldon Has Gone Before.
这个故事是发生在东德克萨斯州
It's the story of a young boy who is transported
在愚昧无知的边远地区  一个少年郎
from the ignorant backwoods of East Texas
被送到二十三世纪
to the 23rd Century,
在那里  他的聪明才智不仅为人赏识  而且被人盛赞
where his genius is not only appreciated, but celebrated.
杀了我吧
KMN...
现在  在这场关键的戏里
Now, in this pivotal scene,
你扮演的谢尔顿的母亲  与星际联邦的特使
Sheldon's mother, played by you, argues with an emissary
斯波克先生发生争吵  而斯波克先生
of the United Federation of Planets, Mr. Spock,
则由我来生动的展现
the role I will bring to life.
好吧  这样也行  但咱们先试试
Okay, that's fine, but let's try
让你脱离你的舒适区
and get you out of your comfort zone.
为什么咱们要这么做
Why would we want to do that?
"舒适区"之所以这么叫  是有原因的
It's called "the comfort zone" for a reason.
这么做的原因是让你放松点儿
Okay, the whole point of this is to loosen you up a little,
所以我觉得你应该扮演母亲的角色
so I'm thinking you'll play the role of your mother,
而我负责来生动展现斯波克先生
and I will bring life to Mr. Spock.
我没听错吧
I'm sorry.
由你来演斯波克
You'll be Spock?
这才符合逻辑[Spock 台词]
It's only logical.
很好
Very well.
我来叙述一下背景
I'll set the scene.
好的
All right.
东德克萨斯州
"East Texas.
一个温暖的夏夜
"A warm summer night.
一个女人  玛丽
"A woman, Mary,
站在阳台上
"stands on a porch.
从远处传来  火车孤独的汽笛声
In the distance, we hear a lonesome train whistle..."
知了单调的嗡嗡声
"The droning buzz of cicadas..""
一只土狼冲着月亮嗷嚎
"A coyote howls at the moon,
吓唬着四面八方心灵脆弱的少年郎
frightening sensitive young boys everywhere."
在丛林之外
"Out in the woods,
-一只猫头鹰发出毛骨悚然的尖叫声  -够了够了
- an owl screeches..." - Okay, okay.
我懂了  你的背景叙述得很清楚了
We get it. You set the scene.
呜呼
Hoo!
快念你母亲角色的台词吧
Now just read your mother's line.
"谢利
"Shelly!
谢利  我跟你说过多少遍了
"Shelly, how many times have I told you
别把你的实验工具放在阳台"
"not to leave your sciencey stuff out on the porch?
"天啊
"Goodness,
我永远都不懂这孩子"
"I'll never understand that boy.
"不过再次声明  我是宗教迷
"But then again, I'm a religious nut,
我的心灵已经把太多东西拒之门外了"
and my mind is closed to so many things."
"斯波克呼叫进取号  发送成功"
"Spock to Enterprise. Transport successful."
"荣耀归于上天
"Glory be to Heaven,
某种不知名物体突然出现"
"some sort of creature just manifested out of thin air.
"乔治  把你那装满威士忌的百事可乐罐放下
"George, put down that Pepsi can full of bourbon
有时间做模作样  还不如赶紧把抢抗上呢"
that ain't foolin' no one, and get your shotgun!"
"向你问候  玛丽·库珀
"Greetings, Mary Cooper.
我是斯波克"
I am Spock."
抱歉  我还是接受不了
I'm sorry. I just don't buy it.
别停  继续演
Just keep going!
"天啊  你的突然出现吓坏我了"
"Oh, my, your sudden appearance startles me."
"我们在遥远的二十三世纪里
"We have been monitoring your son Sheldon
一直密切关注着你的儿子  谢尔顿"
"from the 23rd Century, and
"我们认为他现在已经够格
"we have determined that he is now ready
加入我们的行列"
"to join us.
"他独一无二的聪明才智  是能给我们
"His unique genius is our best hope
广阔而混乱的星系  带来和平的最大希望"
for bringing peace to a vast and troubled galaxy."
"我懂"
"I understand.
"谢利
"Oh, Shelly?
有个男人说要把你带去未来
"A man's here to take you away to the future!
收拾的时候  记得带上干净的内裤哦"
Be sure to pack clean underwear."
好  很好  咱们再试试最后那段台词
Okay, okay, let's try that last line again,
这次你可以试着稍微带点哽咽
and this time, maybe try choking up a little.
为毛
Why?
你都快失去自己儿子了
Well, you're losing your son.
没错  但是他将要去一个更好的地方
Yes, but he's going to a better place
在那里他不会被人打击得  那么厉害
where he won't get beat up... so much.
拜托啦  试着按我说的演一把
All right, come on, just try it my way.
假装你很舍不得他走
Pretend you're sad to see him go.
我会带你入戏的
I'm gonna lead you in.
"他独一无二的聪明才智  是能给我们
"His unique genius is our best hope
广阔而混乱的星系  带来和平的最大希望"
for bringing peace to a vast and troubled galaxy."
-该你了  -抱歉  即使你演技浮夸了点
- That's your cue. - I'm sorry. I just love that line.
但我依然爱这句台词爱到死
Even the way you do it.
算了  快点  快点
All right, come on, come on.
放点真感情进去
Put some real emotion into it.
此处省略23个字
Blah-blah, blah, blah...
从"带来和平的最大希望"  开始
"vast and troubled galaxy." Go.
"谢利
"Oh, Shelly?
有个男人说要把你带去未来
A man's here to take you away to the future""
收拾的时候  记得带上干净的内裤哦"
"Be sure to pack clean underwear."
很好很好  做得不错
That's good. That's good. That's good.
妈咪  你为什么哭
Mommy, why are you crying?
因为我会很想你  谢利豆
'Cause I'm gonna miss you, Shelly-bean,
即使你总是吓死我
even though you creep the bugeeses out of me.
好  我猜现在开始即兴表演了
Okay, I guess we're improvising now.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这不能怪我
It's not my fault.
我只是太过聪明了
I'm just incredibly smart,
而这里的每一个人  都蠢得跟一坨大便一样
and everyone around here is dumber than a bag of rocks.
又来了  你怎么又哭上了
Oh, now, don't you start crying.
你快上那艘破飞船
You get in that spaceship.
妈咪去赌场要迟到了
Mommy's late for Indian bingo.
库珀太太  我是佩妮
Mrs. Cooper, hey, it's Penny.
我想我让你儿子崩溃了
Yeah, I think I broke your son.
等等
Hey, hold on.
你妈咪的电话
Talk to your mother.
妈咪  我爱你
Mommy, I love you.
拜托别让斯波克把我带去未来
Don't let Spock take me to the future!
拉杰
Hey, Raj,
我知道你在刻意避开我和霍华德
I know you've been avoiding me and Howard,
除非你告诉我  你的小脑袋到底在想什么
and I'm not leaving until you tell me what's going on
否则我是不会走的
inside that little head of yours.
* 就象狂野的大象 *
* Like the wild elephant *
* 我要大声宣告我对你的爱 *
* I am trumpeting my love for you *
* 就像隐藏的鲜花 *
* Like a hidden flower *
* 我香甜的芬芳要开启你全新的视觉 *
* My sweet fragrance comes into view *
* 我的心好比正午的太阳  为你而炙热发烫 *
* My heart burns for you like the sun at noon *
* 我的心好比热情的沙漠  迎接你这场及时雨*
* My desert welcomes you like the rainy monsoon *
* 你是我的小心肝 *
* You are my heart *
* 主宰我的小宇宙 *
* My universe *
* 你是我的小心肝 *
* You are my heart *
* 主宰我的小宇宙 *
* My universe *
* 你是我的小心肝 *
* You are my heart *
* 主宰我的小宇宙 *
* My universe *
* 你是我的小心肝 *
* You are my heart *
* 主宰我的小宇宙 *
* My universe *
* 你是我的小心肝 *
* You are my heart *
* 主宰我的小宇宙 *
* My universe *
撇开宝莱坞式歌舞不说  哥绝对不是小基佬
Dance number aside, I'm so not gay.